I was on a losing streak at the
beginning of this year. I lost a little
bit over six figures. So, I decided to
take things serious and I locked myself
in a room until I made a little bit over
a million
dollars. This is exactly how it went
out. So, to start off, how did I lose
multiple six figures in the market?
Well, I decided to have a bright idea to
send free signals, not only by myself,
but to join with one of my really good
friends, Sensei, and let's create a free
community where we're going to be giving
out free signals every single day. I
give swing/day trades and he gives scalp
trades. We're both profitable traders.
We both have a great track record. It's
a great idea for us to combine and give
free signals. Now, the problem that
ended up happening is that Sensei and I
never saw eye to eye. So decided to
basically part ways and I decided to
continue the legacy going of the free
signals and the free trades. So I
decided to send every single one of my
trades in my telegram and host a live
stream Monday, Wednesday, Friday where I
shared every single one of these trades
and broke them down in detail until I
made a million dollars. I was not going
to let the losing streak despite the
pressure and despite the association
with Sensei get to me at all. I know my
profitability. I know my strategy and I
know my trading plan works. I'm going to
keep that going. So that's exactly what
I did. Did a new signal group with all
of my community members completely for
free. And these live stream I broke down
every single trade to the tea. And there
I realized two very key important
factors. One, even though I'm a great
trader, I'm a great trader by myself in
my room in my office. the moment that I
have to send out a trade and I see
150,000 people copying this exact same
trade and I get tens of thousands of DMs
every single day and people giving me
their own comments on the trade that I'm
sending. Oh, you're doing it right or
you're doing it wrong or this added
pressure was something that I did not
account for before we decided to come
together with Sensei and I. So that
pressure combined didn't help. And two,
a perfect coincidential timing to go
against us is Trump had come right into
the markets right at the beginning of
the year and we didn't really realize
the impact he was going to have because
we've been killing the markets for the
last four years trading in the Biden
markets. Biden markets were very slow,
very predictable because he wasn't
really doing anything honestly and that
was very easy to trade. and Trump comes
into the markets and the markets take
complete turn of events all across the
board and we weren't ready for that as
traders especially as signal providers
because we're used to certain type of
markets and as soon as we're about to
send these signals we get a completely
different type of market. So our
strategies hadn't adapted to that
massive shift in the market. So to
summarize my negative start to the year
with this losing streak, it basically
comes down to the major shift into the
markets of Trump coming in and shifting
the markets completely and that caught
us by surprise. Sensei and I not seeing
eye to eye, I had to pick up for his
slack. He basically didn't really want
to do it. And then you add on top of
that the pressure of having over 100,000
people watching every single one of your
trades. It got to us and I decided that
I didn't want to keep having to carry
for Sensei's weight. So that's where I
decided to lock myself in a room and
share every single one of my trades and
host a live stream three times a week
until I made over a million dollars. And
I [__] did it. Now, obviously making
a million dollars might seem
challenging, but it's really not if you
don't have a plan. And I made a very
strategic plan before I got into it
because I wanted to actually not only
execute, but succeed in it. And I
learned from the lessons that I did when
I was partnered up with Sensei
previously. So to make these million
dollars, I first have to have a very
powerful riskmanagement strategy. So
every single time I'm going to take a
trade, I'm going to risk anywhere from
200 to around
$300,000. And I'm going to target
anywhere from $400 to $600,000. Meaning
my risk-to-reward is a 1 to2 one to
three. Now it makes no difference if I'm
risking $20,000, $2,000, or $200,000.
The risk-to-reward remains the same. If
I risk 2,000 is to gain $4,000. If I
risk 3,000, it's to gain 6,000. It's the
exact same risk management on dollar
amount, but just on a lot higher dollar
amount. And this is something that I've
been applying for the last 7 years that
I'm sure every single one of you guys
apply when you go past a challenge or
you go trade on your personal account.
You have to have risk manager. Mine just
happens to be on a very high dollar
amount or at least it's high to me. And
another thing is a lot of you guys are
curious is how much I actually have in
my trading account on this challenge
that I'm doing. And I didn't disclose of
it because you guys should not be
focusing on how much money I have in my
account. You should be focusing on the
trades that I'm literally predicting day
after day on these live streams. A lot
of people were curious, but how much
money did you start with or why are you
hiding your account balance? Well, cuz I
don't have to show it. I don't have to
tell you guys how much in my account.
It's like me showing you how much I have
in my bank account. like it's not
necessary and I feel like I kind of
spoiled a lot of people because at the
beginning of the year I did show a $2
million account which respectfully is
not my biggest account and I decided to
just keep that to myself because some
people believe that it's not realistic
even though I'm showing it's a live
account. I rather just show you guys
that I'm predicting the trades, how I
enter, how I going to draw them and then
how I go into profit. I don't really
have to show you guys the account size.
It's irrelevant to the trade. It's
irrelevant to you. Focus on your trade.
Don't focus on my money. how deep my
pockets go aren't going to make any
difference on if the trade's going to go
to the stop- loss or take profit. Just
focus on the trade. And to focus on my
trades, let's go right into the first
one, which actually happened to be a
break even trade, which actually was a
trade that was in profit $415,000.
Obviously, if I were to expect for this,
I would have closed at $400,000 of
profit. But since I did not, I decided
to continue to hold and it came back and
took me out at break even. Did it suck?
Yes. GBPCHF was a major counter trend
trade. This is a trade that I would
normally never take and I explained this
multiple times in the live streams
inside of my Telegram on Instagram and I
explained why that the market is
bearish. The weekly is bearish, daily is
bearish, 4 hours bearish. We should not
be buying a market that is overall
bearish. It actually goes completely
against my strategy. But what my
strategy does go for is when patterns
repeat themselves. There was a major
pattern that this market was about to
create and it created it to the tea.
That is a reversal pattern. Market was
at the lowest point that it has ever
been. It's been at the lowest point and
every single time it gets there, it has
a major retracement to the upside. This
would be the trade that if you're going
to take against the trend is the one
that makes the most amount of sense.
We're at the lowest point we've ever
been in history. We could go to a
different server if you want. Like we go
to F. Watch. Look, we're going to go to
GBPCHF on FXCM, which they have more
history. It created the same double
bearish weekly approach. One weekly
bullish consolidation candlestick. And
then the following one should be a
bullish engulfing to have the
retracement. It did that four times in
the past. I pointed it out multiple
different times. And this should be the
next time. There's no reason why it
shouldn't. And there's no reason why it
should go lower because it's never gone
lower. I'm anticipating for a bounce up
basically from this support level. It
was real. My only confluence in the
pattern that it has done it in the past.
We enter the trade after a beautiful
morning star formation posted
everywhere. Everybody enters the trade
alongside with us. And I have a takerit
set on a minor 4hour take-profit zone.
The trade gets to my one to two
risk-to-reward. So I risk $200,000 on
the trade. I'm up $400,000 because I'm
at a one to2. And as I'm looking at the
trade, I'm like, hm, this has the
potential to actually make it to a one
to4 risk-to-reward because it has a lot
more to have a retracement. But not
going to lie, I got a little bit blinded
because it was the first trade that I
sent out for free with the live stream.
Everybody was winning and I want people
to win more without having to add more
risk. you could have gotten another two
risk-to-reward on top of this trade
without adding another position. And I
don't know about you guys, but I'm all
for free money without having to risk
any more money. What's the worst that
can happen? Takes me out of break even.
Okay, that's perfect with me. And that's
exactly what it did. We bought, we hit
the one to two risk-to-reward. You guys
already know I decided to add more
profits to this without adding any extra
risk. And we obviously came back, took
me out at break even. I am not the type
of person to go break even ever for a
situation just like this because if this
trade did not present to me the exact
same entry signal that it did at this
point right here, I would have not
entered this trade at this area right
here. I would have literally just missed
quote unquote missed out on the trade.
price came back, took me at a break
even. And the most ironic part is that
the break even was actually in profit
$10,000. I always put a little bit above
my entry just to cover swap fees,
commissions, spread, everything just so
I can have a little bit of just actual
break even or even a little bit of
profit. And I got a DM from a couple
people and it's like, "Bro, I can't
believe that you're calling a $10,000
profit a break even day. That's what I
want to make a month." And I reflected
for a second. And I'm like, damn. I
remember when I started trading, I
wanted to make $10,000 a month and then
maybe scale to $50,000 a month and then
$100,000 a month. And now for me,
$10,000 is a break even trade. It was
just almost like a full circle moment
where I kind of realized, oh [__] I I
think I made it. And what got me to this
point is following my trading plan. I
did not care that I was up $400,000 and
then the trade took me back at break
even. That was part of my trading plan.
and sticking to the trading plan won me
my next trade back on GBPCHF. The most
ironic part about this is that I set it
on the live stream. If GBPCHF comes back
for whatever reason, takes me out at
break even and I get the exact same
entry signal. I'm going to take the
exact same trade again. I literally copy
paste a risk to reward. I the entry was
different by about seven pips. Stop loss
different by seven pips. Take profit
exactly the same. And guess what I did?
I did the exact same thing. Stuck to my
trading plan and I took the trade and
the trade went right back straight into
profit. Both of these trades had zero
draw down and went straight into profit.
And when this trade was at $400,000 in
profit, I was going to make the exact
same decision. You know what? I see this
trade to have potential to make it to a
1 to4 where then I could obviously
double my profit without having to add
any risk. But there was one factor that
was very different and that is that we
were approaching the weekend. So it was
already going into Friday and I decided,
you know what? I don't want to hold this
position. I want to end off the week
profitable. Let's close out this trade
right here. So I closed out the first
trade for a little bit over $400,000 in
profit. And it was the exact same trade
that I had just taken. And ladies and
gentlemen, we have officially closed the
a winning or I have officially closed a
winning position. Technically, right
now, we are only up about 200,000
because I lost 200,000 the first week,
made 400 this week. That led us in
profit 200. So, I kind of got a little
bit emotional and this is obviously
happened over the course of the weekend
as I'm talking to my community members.
Whereas I could have closed the first
trade for $400,000 in profit and I could
have closed the second trade for
$400,000 in profit. Meaning on the first
week I'd be 80% of the goal. And looking
back at it like that, it sucked a little
bit because I could have finished a lot
faster. But you know what? Everything
happens for a reason. And if that's what
I meant to do by sticking to my plan, so
be it. And the irony of this GPCHF trade
is on Monday when it reopened, price
came back, would have taken me out at
break even and then it would have flown
straight to the final take profit that I
have been wanting to hold the whole
entire time for a 1 to4 risk-to-reward.
So if I decided to hold and put my at
break even would have taken me out of
break even and I would have probably not
entered again because it did not give me
the exact same entry signal how I wanted
to. But the overall direction and the
prediction of the analysis was to the
tea. It decided just to take longer than
it should have. So after I realized that
I could have been 80% of the goal there
and I'm actually only 40% of the goal
there by just taking two trades. First
trade being break even. Second trade
closing at $400,000 in profit. The third
trade I'm kind of little a bit
aggressive. I'm not going to lie. I'm
ready to basically eat the market and
take the first opportunity to present
itself. And doing that, it bit me in the
ass and I lost. I lost our third trade
on Euro AUD. Euro AUD. So this is
[__] bro. This is so [__]
annoying. Euro AUD was a very similar
trade to GBPCHF in terms of risk. It was
a higherend risk trade as well simply
because we were trading against the
trends. Now, I don't happen to do this
all the time, but when the opportunity
is there and it makes sense, it simply
makes sense. Euro EUD weekly time frame
was bullish, daily time frame was
bullish, but the 4hour time frame was
bearish. For me to take a trade
according to my strategy, I need a
minimum of two consecutive time frames
in sync and I trade with that direction.
Technically, if the weekly and the daily
are bullish, I should be looking for
buys. But the weekly was at a higher
high, the daily was at a higher high.
The price needs a retracement. If
Bitcoin is at $100,000, you're not going
to buy a Bitcoin at $100,000. You're
going to wait for it to come back a
little bit and then buy. That the exact
same thing happened with your AD. It was
at a very high point that I'm expecting
for this retracement. And I decided to
take it a little bit early because I did
not wait for as much daily accumulation
as I would have wanted to. And Euro AUD
basically went straight to my stop loss,
went above it by about 10 pips, and then
went straight to my takerit. Now, does
that suck? Yes, because I don't ever
want to lose a trade and especially in
front of everybody while I'm showing
this on a live stream and sharing it and
everybody copying it. But it was a
lesson for me just because I won a trade
and even though I missed out on more
profits than I should have, I shouldn't
be obviously super aggressive to take
the next one. And if I'm going to have a
trade be a counter trend trade, have the
most amount of confirmations that I
possibly have. And these are things that
obviously I know I've been trading for
the market forever. But sometimes I need
this quick humbling moments and have
people see me make this mistake in front
of them and me almost be kind of
humiliated by it and not want to make
that mistake in front of people again.
So they held me accountable for it. And
this loss was a little bit over
$150,000. So it set us back to about
$300,000 $280,000 on the account. And
after it takes me out by about 10 pips,
it literally goes straight to the
takerit where I would have made other
$400,000. Meaning I could have been at
that very moment in profit $800,000. And
if I would have closed every single
trade in profit, I would have been up 1
to $1.3 million. So like all this is
going through my mind. And the crazy
part about it is that everybody's seeing
it on the live streams. Beauty of this
is you guys are literally going to know
exactly the type of trade that I'm going
to be looking to enter, why I'm looking
to enter, where I'm looking to enter, my
stop loss, take profit, the reasoning
behind it, and you guys are going to see
it live every other day of the week. You
guys are going to get the start of the
week on Monday essentially, and then
update middle of the week and then recap
at the end of the week on Friday. It
[__] doesn't get any better than
this. your boy. I literally been able to
tell and do their own calculations on
how much I would be up if I didn't get
wicked out by 10 pips and if I didn't
get stopped out at break even. Trust me,
it's not a good look. So, at this point
in the challenge, I basically have had
every single scenario happen. I've had a
break even, I've had a win, and I've had
a wick out loss. Well, technically, I
haven't had a full loss, which I don't
mind those. I hate the wickouts, but
it's okay. But nothing like the next
trade, which is AUD CAD, which was
probably the craziest swing I've had in
a very long time. This trade was a
perfect, beautiful analysis. Right now,
where we are is literally at this
candlestick right here. We're waiting
for this candlestick to be made. We
already have the pull-up, the dogee.
Now, we're expecting for this right
here. So, we have to wait for that wick
to be created. That wick is what's going
to save us from taking a loss or not.
And if we manage to hold through it long
enough and not get caught on that wick
out of the move, I believe we're going
to have a very very very high
risk-to-reward paying trade. ADCAD was
at a very strong daily level of support.
It was being used as resistance. The
weekly is bearish. Daily is bearish.
4hour had been accumulating there for
nearly 2 weeks. Meaning that we have
clearly rejected this very strong level
of support being used as resistance. I
have my two consecutive time frames in
sync. I have my strong area of interest.
So, I have my entry signal, everything I
look for in a trade. Price gives me my
entry signal. I enter the trade, go into
a little bit of draw down, and then we
start going into profit. Everything is
good. I'm $100,000 in profit. 200,000,
300,000, 400,000 here. I've always kept
very excited, posting on Instagram. We
[__] made it. We're almost there.
Then we are about $500,000 in profit.
$550,000 in profit, $600,000 in profit.
So, I think I was shy at that point
around 80 $90,000 to close out the trade
and complete it. And I'm looking at my
DMs. Everybody's saying close, close,
close, close. I'm like, guys, why would
I close? I'm only $80,000 away. I'm
going to continue to set and forget
until it hits how much? I think I needed
about $680,000 690,000 in order for me
to close at a million in profit because
I'm only in profit at that point about
$300,000 because I took that loss on
Euro AUD and I decided to go break my
fast, hit the gym. When I go back and
look at my phone, I was around $200,000
in profit. Price had completely reversed
and never made it to my take-profit
point. I was shy by $80,000. Everybody's
seeing this and they're telling me to
close and I'm sticking to my plan. I
said, you know what? I'm not going to
close. I'm going to stick to my plan.
Price goes back $200,000 in profit,
$100,000 in profit, break even, negative
$50,000, negative $100,000. And this is
by London session. So throughout the
course of the whole entire day, I see my
profits disappear into negative. So, I'm
not mad that the trade didn't have the
move because I don't anticipate the
move. I'm mad that it didn't, you know,
kind of react to that. I feel like I
could have been a little bit more
conservative with my take-profit. I
could have literally put my takeprofit
to maybe even this structure point right
here. And that's still 1 to 2.5 risk to
reward, but I'm I'm chasing the money so
bad. And since I'm chasing that monetary
goal, I'm not making logical trades. And
that's the pro like I'm I'm doing a
mistake that rookie traders do. I'm
doing a mistake that uh traders that are
not profitable yet do because they
continue to chase the money and not
close the trade for what the trade is.
That's what I should have done here. I
should have closed the trade. I'm at 1
to2 1 to 2.5 for what it is and
realizing that the higher time frames,
yes, they are destined to continue going
to the downside, but it's probably not
going to happen this week. should happen
sometime next week. And a lot of people
ask, why didn't you go break even? Well,
because the daily time frame hadn't
closed. I like to wait for the daily
time frame to close to see if I go break
even or not because based off of where I
can potentially project if it's going to
have a wick retracement, that's where I
put my break even. It's very technical
stuff. Talk about it in the live stream,
so you guys should definitely check it
out. But I decided to not go break even
and just to continue to hold the trade
because I accepted the risk. And the
trade goes into draw down a little bit
over
$120,000. Now, imagine that feeling that
you're $80,000 away from the goal and
then you go into negative
$120,000. How do you feel? How do you
then go on another live stream the next
day and say, "Guys, set and forget,
continue to do this."
Well, I did it. And that is by sticking
to my plan. And guess what? and AUD CAD.
I mean, I think I think all of the
market right now is looking at AUD CAD
and seeing what is about to happen. So,
sticking to my plan, made the trade go
back into profit. $100,000, 200, 300,
400, all the way back until
$550,000. When the trade is back in that
profit, I said, "Okay, boom. We're
done." Closing right here because it was
at my 1 to2 risk-to-reward. Anything
below that, I considered that I was
going to be greedy and I'm just chasing
the money at this point. I'm doing it
for the money. I'm not doing it for the
trade. This is something that I'm going
to talk about towards the end of this
and is very important and is my biggest
takeaway from this whole entire thing.
But moral of the story with AUD CAD, we
were almost there, went back into draw
down, and then we went back into profit
and we close in profit for a 1 to2
risk-to-reward for a beautiful half a
million dollar trade. Now, at this
point, I'm probably in profit about
$700,000 roughly, and I need about
$300,000 left in order to complete the
challenge. Now, at this point in the
challenge, I'm probably about 4 weeks
in, almost 12 live streams in, and
probably about 10 missed trades in. So I
obviously I personally executed four
trades at this very moment, but I missed
a little bit over 10 different trades
that I sent out simply because of time
zones, simply because of trading
paralysis, because all the pressure
people watching me. I didn't really want
to take the ultra ultra high risk
trades. There were some other trades I
just overthought about it and I just
decided to only stick to the least
amount of trades that I possibly can
with the higher probability. But at this
point, I've predicted nearly eight to
nine different moves. And obviously,
others were losses that I didn't happen
to take. But I also missed out on about
four different wins. And now that we're
on this last trade, the last winning
trade that we're about to make money
and, you know, complete the
challenge. This is probably the most
disappointing trade that I had. And that
is well, one, we took the exact same
trade that I got stopped out on by 10
pips on Euro AD earlier. and it went
straight to my takerit. I took the exact
same trade again because it came back
into the area, gave me the exact same
entry signal, everything the exact same,
exact same zone, stop loss, take profit,
everything exact same. And I decided to
not only execute it, but executed on a
little bit higher risk. Instead of
risking the regular $200,000 that I was
usually risking, I wanted to risk
$300,000. I execute the $300,000 and the
trade basically goes into a little bit
of draw down, but then goes straight
into take profit. Now, this trade is at
a one:1 risk-to-reward. And when this
trade is at a one:1 risk-to-reward, if I
risk $300,000, I'm up $300,000. All I
need is $300,000 to complete the
challenge. Jordan Welch happens to be at
my house where, you know, doing a video
for his community and he doesn't believe
that by basically one click away, I can
close a position and make
$300,000. And he asked if he could do
it. And I said, "Sure, you can do it."
But I basically am closing this trade
just to complete the challenge. I can
make like 600 700K off the street, but I
don't want it. I just want to make a
million dollars, post it on social
media, and go on vacation, bro. But as
I'm looking at the chart, I see so much
more downside potential from this move
where this one move can easily give me a
million because if I risk $300,000 on
this trade and my risk-to-reward is a 1
to6, I'm nearly making 1.2 million off
of one single trade. But you know what?
At this moment, I'm chasing the money.
I'm chasing the high of finishing the
challenge, getting it done, showing
people how legit I am and how
transparent I am. sharing all these
trade ideas, doing all these live
streams, and Jordan Walsh clicks the
button. Boom. Closes all the trades. I'm
literally just gonna close every single
trade right now. Can I do it? Yeah, you
can do it. Close all. Yeah. Yeah. Make
sure you close this one.
No, no, no. Don't [__] off that one.
This one? Yeah. It's a wrap. That's it.
That's That's $300,000 right there.
Look. All right, chill. So, look. We
just closed at
1.091. So, all the positions that we
were just in right now, it closes
immediately. So, we just made 300. No
way, bro. They going to be in the
comments like, "That's not that's not
real money. That's some that's some fake
platform. That's some fake money." It's
literally real. Alex Gonzalez, LQH live
server. Like, everything is legit. Does
not get more legit than this. N bro,
that's actually insane. I mean, but I've
been in this position since 6:00 in the
morning. It's not like I just entered as
we're walking through the door. That
That would have been [__] crazy. No,
no. Like, I've been in this position for
almost like 5 6 hours. Now, little did I
know that it was probably a cool feeling
for Jordan. At that very moment, I got
butterflies in my stomach. I'm like, I
just [__] up because I had just missed
out on 1.2 million trade. The rest of
the week, I see that trade continuing to
drop and drop and drop and drop without
ever looking back. It never came back
for re-entry. It never came back
anywhere near Jordan closed it off.
meaning I could have just literally done
nothing for the next 2 days and it would
have gone straight to $1.2 million in
profit. And that sucked. But you know
what? It felt good because I can show
people how you can use a profitable
strategy and make money from it. But I
let this be a lesson to myself. So I
don't chase the money. I trade to trade.
I don't trade to make money. When I
trade to make money, it's not following
a plan. It's not organic. And I'm
looking at the money. I'm not looking at
the charts. Looking at the Metatrader
and looking at the money go up and down
does not do anything for the chart. You
looking at the chart will determine if
the money is going to go up or down. But
the candlesticks reflect what's on the
numbers. The numbers don't reflect the
candlesticks. And as soon as I literally
had this realization to myself, I said,
"You know what? I'm no longer going to
trade for the money. I'm going to keep
trading to trade when it makes sense.
And fine, cost me a million dollars
because I could have just literally
continued to set and forget, which is
what I do all the time. But I decided to
just close it out, complete the
challenge, show people how transparent
it is, how real it is. And if it had to
cost me a million dollars to show
people, I guess it is what it is. But
from this point forward, I am going to
continue to trade to trade and not trade
for the money because it will end up
being more expensive and you won't end
up making any money. And you know, yes,
Euro ED gave me a little bit of PTSD,
right? You know, it made me want to
tattoo set and forget on my forehead so
I can continue to follow my pen how I
should and not do it to show people
because I'm going to complete a
challenge. There's this other trade, USD
CAD. USD CAD was
easily a $700,000 trade that Oh, and
NZDPY was another half a million dollar
trade because they were so beautiful
having all the trend in your favor. They
had the beautiful strong daily area of
interest, 4hour shifted structure and
entry signal at the wrong time for me.
Now this bearish rejection candlestick
happened beautifully engulfing this
other candlestick right here. So this is
a beautiful entry point. If you notice
this happened right before London
session right at 1 in the morning 12:00
p.m. And this would have been a perfect
point for you to enter this trade. Now I
did not enter it and it's going to sound
pretty pathetic but I was not really
paying attention to the charts. like I
was out on the road and I wasn't really
paying attention to it and then I just
saw this bearish move. I'm like, "All
right, cool. I'm going to wait for a
little bit more of a retracement." Came
home and I just knocked out. And on all
of these other retracements, I just
didn't want to enter impulsively and the
trade pretty much just tanked. So, I
personally sometimes I always, you know,
try and wake up at London session as
best as I could. I am human at the end
of the day. Sometimes I just fall
asleep. Sometimes I wake up, sometimes I
just wake up, don't see what I'm
supposed to see, and I missed out on USD
CAD because of a beautiful entry signal
in London session where as soon as 3:00
in the morning came in, flew straight
into take profit for a 1 to 4.5
risk-to-reward. That trade missed
NZDPY, I didn't actually was able to
enter that trade because I was
overleveraged on the loss that I took on
Euro AUD. So that was another trade that
kind of gave me a little PTSD. Imagine
predicting three trades and then you
pick the wrong one. The one the one that
just wicks you out by 10 pips, but then
they all end up going to take profit and
you didn't capitalize off of any of
them. That ended up happening to me
basically every single week with
multiple different pairs. And that is
normal in trading. You're not supposed
to catch them all. Just because you have
one fishing rod, you go out to the ocean
and you see a bunch of fish doesn't mean
you're going to catch all the fish. You
can only fish one rod at a time, one
cast at a time. and either you catch a
big one or you catch a small one or your
line breaks. It's going to happen. It's
part of the process. There's nothing you
can do to avoid it. The best thing that
you can do is be ready to bring it back
up, put another bait, and cast it out
again. But if you want to be that guy,
that fisherman that has multiple
different fishing poles out there,
they're going to get tangled as you're
reeling one in. The fish is pulling down
the other one. Break the rod, you lost
that fish, you lost the rod. But it's
going to cost you more money than just
focusing at one fish at a time. And this
took me a very long time to realize. And
the fish aren't going to go anywhere.
There's plenty of fish in the sea. And
there's always going to be a time to go
out there and catch them. Same exact
thing with the markets. There's plenty
of markets to trade. They're always
going to be there to give you
opportunities. And you only take one
trade at a time. The faster you realize
that and the quicker you take a trade
for a trade and not to make money, the
more money you will make 100%. Just make
sure not to fall asleep and make sure to
set and forget, but don't set and forget
too much. Now, even though this was a
crazy journey for me and it was very
stressful, I'm glad that thousands of
people, tens of thousands of people
capitalized off of this. Uh you guys can
go see it from yourself. There's
literally tens of live streams of me
showing every single trade, the before,
the during, the after, explaining my
strategy as I'm looking at this trade,
why I'm interested, why I'm not
interested, answering Q&As's at the end,
and just showing you guys how I
personally look at these markets, and
caught a lot of people by surprise
because nobody knew that I did this
constantly. And I do this every single
week with my students where I literally
share the trades just how I did for
people publicly for free. how I did the
live streams. I do this with my
community every single week and I share
the trades and I answer the questions
inside of the community. That's
truthfully why my members have crazy
success numbers. They're making anywhere
from a,000 to $1,500 a week at a minimum
by simply getting on these calls with me
privately and seeing these trades for
themselves and them following alongside
with me. If you guys want to know more
about sudden forget and how these
students are doing stuff like this,
click the link in the description below
because there's a video that explains
for you everything to the tea perfectly
because what I just did right now
publicly, I do it every single week
privately with my students. I just
decided to take on the bigger challenge
and show the masses of people what we're
about inside of the set and forget
community. So, with that being said,
make sure to hit the link in the
description below so you guys can see
what we're about. And make sure to hit
that like and subscribe button because I
don't know anybody else that's putting
on a challenge like this and taking on
all the stress how I did. And I'll do it
again if I have to. That being said,
guys, thank you very much for seeing
this video. Make sure to hit that like
and subscribe button. I'll see you guys
in the next